http://www.pensiondynamics.com/terms

Contact Us
For more information:
News Room
Expect more from your plan?
Request a Quote
Has your plan been reviewed lately?
Request a Complimentary Benchmark Review
Unhappy with your current plan?
Request a Quote
Has your plan been reviewed lately?
Request a Complimentary Benchmark Review
Terms
Securities offered through Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation, member FINRA.
Copyright and Trademark
The copyright in all material provided on this website is held by Pension Dynamics Company LLC. Any unauthorized use of any material contained on this website may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. None of the material on this website may be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted or transmitted in any form or by any means, including, but not limited to, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording, or otherwise, without the prior written permission of Pension Dynamics Company LLC.
Privacy
At Pension Dynamics Company LLC and Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation, we respect your right to privacy and data security. That's why, when you visit our website any information you provide will be kept strictly confidential. We do not sell, rent or disclose your information to anyone.
How do we protect your information?
We exercise great care to protect your personal information. This includes, among other things, using industry standard techniques such as firewalls, intrusion detection and website monitoring. However, the security of information transmitted through the Internet can never be guaranteed. This is especially true for information you transmit to us via e-mail. We have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our servers.
How is information collected, used, and disclosed?
We do not collect personal information—unless we first ask you for it. We may request that you voluntarily supply us with information, including your e-mail address or telephone number so that we may respond to your requests. Whether you provide any information is entirely up to you. If you have voluntarily provided information, you consented to the collection and use of your personally identifiable information as described in this Terms of Use Statement.
Pension Dynamics Company LLC and/or Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation may disclose information in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the Website Terms of Use; or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.
Website Statistics
Pension Dynamics Company LLC and/or Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation may gather aggregate statistics about visitors to our website, such as volume, traffic patterns, and related website information, but these statistics will include no personally identifiable information.
The Pension Dynamics Company LLC website, like many other commercial websites, may utilize a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how our website is used. These cookies are designed to help remember any preferences that may have been set while the visitor was browsing the website. Cookies are small strings of text that websites can send to your browser. Cookies cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or obtain your e-mail address. If you are simply browsing the Pension Dynamics Company LLC website, a cookie may be used to identify your browser as one that has visited the website before.
Laws and Regulations
Access to and use of this website is subject to all applicable international, federal, state, and local laws and regulations. User agrees not to use the website in any way, which violates such laws or regulations.
Limitation of Liability
Under no circumstances shall Pension Dynamics Company LLC and/or Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation be liable for any damages suffered by you (the web visitor), including any incidental, special or consequential damages (including, without limitation, any lost profits or damages) even if Pension Dynamics Company LLC and/or Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation was advised of the possibility of such damages.
No Warranties
Information and documents provided on this website are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including without limitation warranties of merchantability, fitness or a particular purpose, and non-infringement. Pension Dynamics Company LLC uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this website; it does not; however, make any warranties or representations as to its accuracy or completeness. Pension Dynamics Company LLC periodically adds, changes, improves, or updates the information and documents on this website without notice. Pension Dynamics Company LLC assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of this website. Visitors use this website at your own risk.
As an independent employee retirement and benefits firm with deep plan expertise and experience, Pension Dynamics is uniquely qualified to design and administer your employee retirement and benefit plan.
Get In Touch
Contact Us
Contact
Contact
Contact Us
925.956.0505M-F: 8am - 5pm PST
925.956.0506
Quick Links
Copyright 2018 © Pension Dynamics Company LLC. All rights reserved.
Securities offered through Pension Dynamics Securities Corporation, member FINRA.
Research our firm with FINRA's BrokerCheck
.
Investment Advisory Services offered through Stephen James Butler LLC.
Footer menu
Terms
Business Continuity
Contact
